这到底是什么地方
What is this place?
我怎么了
What's wrong with me?!
嘿，嘿，来
Hey, hey, hey, here...
不过是穿越后遗症而已，看
It's just a little bit of transcendental sickness. Look...
好吧
Okay...
对不起
Sorry...
那到底是啥
What the hell was that?
我救了你好吗
I just saved your life!
像你这种非元素的娃
Non-Elemental boys like yourself can't pass
穿越平面是不可能没点反应的
from one plane to the next without getting sick.
下站就和之前一样
Next stop same as the last!
终点站就和下站一样
Last stop same before next!
把你的票准备好
Get your tickets ready please!
嘿
Hey!
我们在找一个妹子，她叫Bo
We're looking for a woman. Her name is Bo...
哇
Whoa!
没什么好紧张的童鞋们
Nothing to worry about folks!
司机大概没戴眼镜
The engineer must have forgotten his glasses!
嘿
Hey!
是我的错觉么，说到Bo的时候整列车都在晃
Is it me or did this entire train just shake at the mention of Bo's name?
啊
Ah...
尖叫
The screams...
被诅咒禁锢的灵魂想要出去
damned souls are trapped and they're trying to get out.
我们得逃出去找你的妹子
We gotta get out of here and find your girl.
来
Come on.
你能不能别拉着个脸
Would you please stop with the attitude?
我讨厌这地方
I hate this place.
又没有无线  还特么这么恶心
There's no WIFI or anything,and it's a shit-hole!
不过是一晚上而已
It's just gonna be for one night.
在这别动
Stay here...
家
Home?
干嘛？
What?
总得有人做点什么吧
Someone had to do something.
本作品片源来自互联网，仅供个人影视制作学习交流之用
任何组织和个人不得公开传播或用于任何商业盈利用途
挪威金毛的胡须最有爱了字幕组  r(st)q
英文字幕：来自互联网
翻译：Neffititi 骷髅头正宫_K 李夹碎 Momou各N大
精校：Neffititi Joy 李夹碎    压制：潜行的五
发布：百度贴吧Tamsin后援群
资源下载请关注瓦尔基里字幕组官方微博
4x03 Lovers. Apart.
往左是松，往右是紧
Lefty loosey.Righty tighty.
*双向螺丝刀的使用口诀，往左是松，往右是紧*
见过你妈穿睡裙
Seen your mother in her nighty.
哦，原来问题根源在这里
Oh, there's the little trouble maker.
能为你效劳吗，小姐
Can I help you, young lady?
想念你留在波兰的钢琴，是吧
You miss the piano that you left back in Poland, don't you?
真遗憾
Pity.
本来可以把你捧红的
I could have made you a star.
尼玛
Holy crap!
你干啥了
What did you do?
重新整理了下
A little reorganizing.
看上去还行吗
Is it okay?
还行
Okay?
这地方比我公寓还整洁
This place is more organized than my shitty apartment.
恩
Um...
糖和胡椒、盐放一起
sugar is with salt and pepper.
显然
Obviously.
还有，恩，醋和番茄酱还有别的调味品放一起
And, um, vinegar is with ketchup and other condiments.
哦 然后不再是放小苏打旁边了
Oh! And no longer directly next to the baking soda
你可以想像我看到那个的时候有多惊讶
...you can imagine my surprise when I saw that...
任何人都会很惊讶
actually everybody's surprised
要是那俩混合在一起
if those two decide to mix it up and have a party.
碳酸非常不稳定
Carbonic acid is actually very unstable ...
就像这地方和，Ronald
kind of like this place ...and Ronald.
你真幽默
You're hilarious.
我有吗
Am I?
那么，你喜欢么
So? You like?
当然，我太喜欢了
Yeah.I do like.
我就需要点糖
I just need some sugar.
*Sugar语意也有接吻的意思*
Crystal   我不能
Crystal... I can't.
休息够了 休息够了
Break's over! Break's over!!!
看吧
See?
不稳定
Unstable.
看吧
See.
幽默
Funny.
你们在火车上吗
Were you on the train?
什么火车
What train?
妈……“火车”是指海洛因好吗
Mom..."train" is obviously slang for heroin.
*train 俚语中指海洛因*
我是说 看看她那样子
I mean, just look at her.
嗨,我叫Kathy
Hi, my name is Kathy.
这是我活力无限的女儿 Julia
and this is my...energetic daughter, Julia.
他干吗那么走路
Why is he walking like that?
这是Jenkins家族古老的迷信
Oh, it's an old Jenkins family superstition.
真是有趣的周末
Makes for a fun weekend.
那些烟去哪了
Where did all the smoke go?
有人把玻璃打碎了
Somebody broke all those glasses.
大姐 我觉得你的脑子坏掉了
Bitch, I think your brain broke …
Julia！
Julia!
这和Lauren有关吗
Does this have something to do with Lauren?
哦天哪我为什么不记得了
Oh, God...why can't I remember, I...
噢
Ow!
谁打我了
Did somebody hit me?
我妈
Mom did.
哦 神啊
Oh, God...
哦神啊 我好饿
Oh, God, I am so hungry.
你要吃点什么吗
Would you like something to eat?
哦 拜托别问这个
Oh, please do not ask me that.
杀了他们 全部都杀掉
Kill them...Kill them all...
杀了他们
Kill them.
噢,振作点, Dennis
Oh...Keep it together, Dennis.
好 鞋子都挂起来了
Okay...shoes are all hung...
Ian  我们的客人醒了
Ian...our guest is awake.
恩  你别好像盯着热狗肠一样盯着我爸看好吗
Uh, can you not look at my Dad like he's made out of hotdogs?
姑娘
Young lady …
没什么
It's okay.
她让我想起我的闺蜜
She reminds me of my best friend.
满窝心的
It's comforting.
那个 不是说我们不欢迎你 但你必须得离开
Look, I don't mean to be rude, but you need to go...
爸 她都快死了好吗 真是的
Dad. She's practically a dead person. Jesus.
她现在必须得离开
She needs to go.Now.
Ian 她还没吃东西呢
Ian, she hasn't had anything...
姑娘们
Girls!!!
现在
Now!
我能先去个洗手间吗
Can I use the ladies room first?
这是她的房间
This was her room.
她在这呆过
She was here.
嘿 醒醒
Hey! Wake up!
把你弄昏的那个妹子
The girl that did this to you…
她的吻技太棒了
She's such a good kisser...
她在哪
Where is she?!
Bo在哪
Where's Bo?!
要是发现她不见了 他会气疯的
He's gonna be so angry when he finds out she's gone...
Bo
Bo!!!
这是她的
This was hers.
她跳车的时候要是像你刚才那么难受
If she jumped from the sickness that you had
那简直只是个开始
a minute ago, it's just the tip of the iceberg.
精神错乱和腹痛会弄死她的
The delirium and the stomach cramps are gonna lead to death.
可我没事
But I'm fine!
因为你和我在一起 而我是元素妖精
Because you're with me, an Elemental.
这辆火车很特别
And this train is special.
要是没有邀请就来去的话
If you leave or enter without an invitation ...
起码也得有个锚
or at least an anchor...
但你能救她 对吗
But you could save her, right?
我不知道 大概吧
I don't know.Maybe...
你行的 来吧
You can do this, come on...
系好安全带吧 情圣
Fasten your seat belt, Lover Boy.
你在这下面干什么
What the hell are you doing down here?
看来你不是什么年度最佳爹地啊  Ian
Not so much father of the year, are we, Ian?
你觉得你随便就能囚禁别人
You think you can just hold people against their will? Huh?
你把你女儿当囚犯吗
You're keeping your daughter prisoner?
你对我一无所知
You don't know anything about me…
我们是在保护Julia
We are protecting Julia.
我才不要你保护我
I don't need you to protect me.
保护她什么
Protect her from what?
不被一个二逼鬼骚扰
A stupid ghost!
再说一遍
Come again?
我们家族被鬼困扰
My family's haunted.
每年的今天她都会出现
Every year on this exact day it comes for us.
这就是为什么我们躲到这地方
That's why we come out here.
远离亲戚朋友 左邻右舍
We get away from neighbors, we get away from families.
把自己锁在房间里 直到早上
We lock ourselves in these cells until morning.
直到鬼走了
Until it's gone.
为什么这个鬼要骚扰你们
Why is a ghost haunting your family?
我不知道 就是家里传下来的
I don't know. I just inherited the damn thing.
在他们能告诉我为啥之前 都死光了
Everyone in my family died before they could tell my why.
好吧 对付怪力乱神可是我的专长
Well, you know dealing with "weird shit" is kinda what I do.
我能帮忙
I can help.
天啊 帮啥
O-M-G, help what?
根本就没鬼好吗 你们这些何弃疗
There is no frigging ghost, you psychos!
每年你都把我关在这个房子里
Every year you lock me up in this stupid house,
我从来就没见过鬼
and I have never even once seen a Ghost!
你不能老关着我吧
You can't keep jailing me away!
好了 时间到了
All right, it's time.
爸爸 不要
Dad! No!
你该离开我的房子了
And it's time for you to leave my house.
你要锁我 就得把我和她锁一起
If I'm locked up ...then she's locked up too.
不能俩人在一个房间 你知道的Julia
You both can't be in the same cell, Julia. You know that!
Ian 她出去了要是走到鞋子和绳结圈的外面怎么办
Ian, what if she goes outside past the shoes and the knots?
*恶灵见到鞋子必然试穿，见到绳结不解完不能动身，因此鞋和绳结圈内是安全的*
我不能拿我女儿的命开玩笑
I am not risking my daughter's life!
你现在赶快走
And you need to leave now!
爸
Dad!
没事
It's ok.
我走就是了
I'll go.
多谢款待
Thank you for everything.
进去
In...
没电话 没信件
No phone calls, no letters.
这漫长的五年来一点联系都没有
No correspondence of any kind. For five long years.
然后突然你离不开我了
And now all of a sudden, you can't live without me.
能说什么呢
What can I say?
我真感动
I'm touched.
要说人生教会了我什么
If there's one thing that life has taught me,
那就是我绝对不需要你
it's that I can definitely live without you.
不过我同意 你被感动了
But, I agree.You are touched.
恩 你看起来有点不同
Now, there is something different about you.
Evony 你染头发了
Evony.Did you dye your hair?
是的 谢谢你注意到了
Yes. Thank you for noticing.
颜色叫做把老娘眼珠长回来
The color is called Grow-My-Eyeball-Back-
否则你就得自己再长出个蛋蛋
Or-You-Will-Be-Growing-Back-A-Ball-Of-Your-Own!
真是好记
That's catchy.
是吧
Isn't it just?
恩
Yeah.
你在教堂合唱团是唱女高音吧
You sing soprano in your church choir don't you?
是女低音
Alto.
哦 我的孩子
Oh.My child...
看来你对付孩子还挺有一套
I see you still have a way with children.
职业病 大概
Hazard of the profession, I suppose.
要是你像我身居高位这么久
When you've been in power as long as I have ...
人人就都是孩子了
everyone is your child.
喜欢与否
Like it or not,
某天你眼一睁就当娘了
one day you just wake up and you're a mother.
另外德鲁依
And Druid.
别像香奈尔糊号香水一样让我失望
Don't disappoint me like 'Chanel Number Goo' did.
*恶搞香奈尔五号香水*
我的眼睛是棕色的
My eyes are brown.
实际上 是帝王棕
Actually, they're imperial brown
角膜边缘有圈淡绿的闪光
with a slight flare of green in the rim of the cornea.
别特么搞砸了
Just don't screw this up.
爸 爸我错了
Dad? Dad, I'm sorry...
嗨
Hey…
你回来了
You came back.
需要个牢伴吗
Need a cell mate?
你没事吧
Are you okay?
你看起来跟健康教育课上生孩子的
You kind of look like that girl from that video
那个恶心录像的女主角一样
in health class giving gross birth.
肯子，没事的
It's fine, Kenz, really.
恩，谁是肯子
Uh, who's Kenz?
显然是一个我很想念的人
Somebody I obviously miss very much.
那个，Julia
Look, um, Julia...
到底是怎么回事
What is going on?
我的家庭团聚经验也不怎么好，相信我
I've been to my share of bad family reunions, believe me,
但你这显然疯得过头了
but this is crazy town.
恩 我能给你看样东西吗
Um, can I show you something?
杀了他们 杀了他们
Kill them...Kill them all.
杀了他们
Kill them...
我的家庭成员 老是离奇死亡
People in my family, keep...they keep dying.
凶杀 自杀
Murder.Suicide.
我的曾祖父
My great grandfather
他差不多毒死了他全家 然后
he poisoned his whole family, almost, and then...
把他们摆得像开茶会的娃娃一样
posed them like dolls that are at a tea party.
恩  然后有这个
Um, and then there's...
这个
there's this.
那个小正太 是我爸
That little boy, right there? That's my Dad.
他看着他爸枪杀全家
He saw his father shoot his entire family.
你知道吗，他老说他继承了这个鬼
You know how he talked about inheriting this ghost?
他会不会其实继承的是这个东西 这个
What if what he actually inherited is this thing? This...
这个东西让他们一直做这些可怕的事
...thing that keeps making them do all this horrible stuff.
你从来没见过异常的东西吗
You've never seen anything out of the ordinary?
他把我锁箱子里好吗 他就是一变态
He locks me in a box, okay? He's sick.
我只是害怕有天他会伤害我们
I'm just scared that one day he's gonna hurt us.
这 可我也爱莫能助
Well, I guess there's nothing I can do.
除了帮你逃出这地方
Except get you out of here.
谢谢你
Oh, thank you.
谢谢你愿意听我说这些
Thank you for listening to me.
你造吗 作为一个闯进我们房子的疯女人来说
You know, for a totally loco chick breaking in our house, you're...
你其实还挺不错的
you're actually pretty cool.
走吧
Come on.
她的气息消失了
We've lost her scent.
不 不 放松 我认识这片森林
No, no, relax...I know these woods.
我的朋友懒酱就埋在这里
My friend Lazy John was buried out here.
他靠着树睡着了 接着
He fell asleep against a tree and then...
猴子们把他埋了
monkeys buried him.
猴子？
Monkeys?
酱 酱
John! John.
酱
John...
你好 酱
Hi, John.
你好 甜心
Hello. Hi, honey.
嗨 Clio
Hi, Clio.
酱
John...
给你介绍一下我的商业伙伴
I would like you to meet my business associate.
酱
John.
商业伙伴
Business Associate.
你有没有看到一只淫妖跑过这片森林？
Have you seen a Succubus running through these woods?
你的淫妖昨晚经过了这里
Your Succubus ran through last night.
但是
But...
她跑去了哪个方向？恩
what direction did she go? Hm.
好的
Okay.
别鄙视我
Don't judge me.
你可以跪添我一只脚趾
You can lick one toe.
不
No!
伦家要舔他
Him.
再说一次？
Come again?
你还想不想找到你的淫妖了 商业伙伴
Do you want to find your Succubus, or not? Business associate.
大兄弟 你真是爱惨这妹子了吧
Man! You must really love this girl.
我们绝不能再提此事
We shall never speak of this again.
那么，这些巫毒符咒到底是干嘛的
So, what's the real story with this voodoo juju?
*Voodoo 起源非洲的巫毒教，在海地，加勒比海地区等盛行*
很明显这个白痴鬼进来之前
Apparently the stupid ghost can't come inside
得先试穿所有鞋子，解开所有绳结，弱爆！
'til she tries on all the shoes and unties all the knots; lame!
那倒着走路又是怎么回事
And walking backwards?
你倒着走的话
Oh, a ghost can't jump inside your body
鬼魂就上不了你的身了 笨
if you're walking backwards, duh.
这很科学
'Cause that makes sense.
噢那不是鬼魂
Oh. That's not a ghost.
那是附身者 Julia
That's a body jumper! Julia!
Julia不
Julia, no!
佛祖啊 你看吧
Jesus!You see.
我告诉过你不要干涉我们
I told you not to interfere!
对不起 我只是想帮忙
Look, I'm sorry. I was just trying to help.
帮忙 我明明已经掌控好局面了
Help?! I had this under control!
Ian!
Julia在哪里失控的
Where did Julia collapse?
外面
Outside.
越过了鞋子和绳结
Past the shoes and knots.
Ian你在干嘛？
Ian, what are you doing?!
我们说了要是谁被上身
We said if this thing entered one of us,
谁就得死
we would kill whoever that was!
可别杀Julia
But not Julia!
我不要她经历
I will not let her live...
我经历过的那些事
with what I had to live with.
Ian 别 她是我们的女儿啊
Ian! Please! She's our baby!
我知道你小时候发生了什么
I know what happened to you when you were young ...
但是还有别的办法的
but there is always another way.
你什么都不知道
You don't know anything!
你不知道这东西对我家人都干了些什么
You don't know what this thing did to my family.
对我的哥哥姐姐 我父母
To my brother, to my sister my mother, my father!
她又让我干了什么
What it made me do.
你
You?
你跟我说那是你父亲干的！
You told me that was your father!
要是Julia要干我干过的那些事
If Julia ever had to do what I did...
你不知道被上身是什么感觉
You don't know what it's like to have something inside of you!
根本无法控制
To have something you just can't control.
实际上 我懂
Actually, yeah, I do.
我能解决
I can fix this.
解决
Fix it?
我还能听见那东西在笑
I can still hear that thing laughing...
我就那样杀了所有我爱的人
...while I butchered everybody that I loved.
你没法战胜纯粹的邪恶
You can't fix pure evil.
他没说错 我就是纯粹的邪恶
He's right. I am pure evil.
我从来就没觉得这么爽过
And I ain't never felt better.
快 躲起来 我不会放任不管的
Go! Hide!I won't let anything happen!
别丢下我们的女儿
Not without our daughter!
我能行
I've got this.
快 快走
Come on, let's go!
小费
Tips.
谢谢
Thanks.
恩恩
Mm-hmm.
我只是思绪纷繁
I just have a lot on my mind.
没事 真的 我懂
It's okay. Really, I get it.
你为什么在这
Why are you here?
恩 我在这工作
Uh... I work here?
对 我知道
Yeah, I know.
只是
It's just that...
我知道Ronald为毛在这
I know why Ronald is here.
我还在思考我为什么在这
And I'm still kinda working on why I'm here...
哦  那个“你为毛在这”的问题
Oh, that 'why are you here'.
你知道吗 要是太私人
You know what,if it's too personal a question...
没关系
It's okay.
恩  好吧 我觉得
Uh...well, I guess...
有时候一个妹子实在太倒霉
...sometimes when a girl's had so much bad luck...
她就觉得 是她的错
she can... start to feel like she's the one causing it.
她就是倒霉本身
She is bad luck.
然后你就开始接受现实
And that's when you start to accept things.
就像小镇上的百灵鸟
Like how being the best singer in town
在大城市屁都不是
doesn't really mean very much in the big city.
伟大的梦想只会吞噬你
And how sometimes big dreams will swallow you whole.
除非你就梦想点小事
If you don't turn 'em into small ones instead.
就像这种小梦想
Small ones like this.
农场出售
Farm for sale?
小农场出售
Small farm for sale.
十亩以下
Just under ten acres.
一些鸡啊 猪啊
Couple of chickens. Pigs.
还有匹名叫公爵的金黄色老马
An old Palomino named Duke.
晨兴理荒秽 带月荷锄归
Work hard all day and just sit and watch the stars at night.
简直就是小天堂
Little heaven right there.
明天见
See you tomorrow.
恩
Mm-hmm.
听着 我知道你现在不愿意和人约会
Listen, I know you're not on the market
但是如果你想喝点啤酒然后
but if you ever wanna grab some beer and...
吃点批萨 发泄下情绪
a pizza and vent...
你知道我住哪儿 随时来找我
you know where I live.
我还真不知道你住哪
I have no idea where you live.
你到底是什么鬼东西
What the hell are you?
腿上功夫还不错嘛
Awesome on two legs.
你是什么异种
And what type of Fae might you be?
恶鬼 恶灵 凶灵 恶魔
Jumbee, Jumbee, Jumbee, Jumbee....
*Jumbee 加勒比海地区对恶灵的统称*
Julia我不想伤害你
Oh, I don't want to hurt you Julia,
但这货一直纠缠不走
but this bitch ain't making it easy.
啊 你是谁啊
Ahhhh! Who the hell are you?
Dyson
Dyson!
他是Dyson 没事了
His name is Dyson.It's okay.
哦天啊 你是怎么找到我的
Oh, God...how did you find me?
我找人帮了点忙
I had a little help.
恶鬼 恶灵 凶灵 恶魔
Jumbee,Jumbee, Jumbee, Jumbee...
Bo 来见见Clio
Bo, meet Clio.
啤酒 披萨 来吐槽吧
The beer and the pizza and the venting.
现在会太早了吗
Is right now too soon?
当然不会咯
Of course not.
快进来
Come on in.
除了上身之外你还有什么其他本事
We know you can body-jump,but what else you got?
哦 我刚才答应三人行了么
Huh...did I just agree to a threesome?
妈 麻麻 他们弄疼我了
Mama!Mama, they're hurting me!
宝贝
Baby!
麻麻
Mom!
不 Kathy
Kathy, no!!!
Kathy
Kathy!!!
不 天啊
No...Oh, God…
芍药
The Peony plant.
哈
What?
芍药能止血
It's gonna stop the bleeding.
这是治疗用的植物
It's healing plant of the Gods.
森林里有
It grows in the forest.
快去
Go!
好
Okay.
Bo 我要带你离开这
Bo...I've got to get you out of here.
你快挂了
You're dying.
这女的才是快死了
This woman is dying.
你不明白 你从那火车上跳下来的时候
No you don't understand. When you jumped from
你病了 你需要帮助
that train, you got sick. You need help.
她才需要帮助 Dyson 这都是我的错
She needs help, Dyson.And it's my fault!
帮我救救她 拜托
Help me fix this, okay?
我坚持的住
I can wait.
坚持压住伤口
Just keep pressure on the wound.
快去追Julia
Go! Get my Julia!
我不能同时失去她们
I can't lose them both!
啊
Ah!
你真是泥菩萨过河自身难保还要救人类
On death's door, and still helping humans...
至少你还是你
at least you're still you.
坚持住坚持住 别离开我
Stay with me...stay with me, stay with me…
哦天哪
Oh, man.
为什么我们不能忘掉一切
Why can't we just.... erase everything.
发生在我们身上的所有坏事情
All the bad shit that's ever happened to us,
或者我们所做的 全部统统忘掉
or that we've done. And just forget it ... all.
忘掉那摸我屁屁的色老板
Forget that horny boss that kept grabbing my ass.
忘掉我大学第一年总是穿着的
Forget the wedding dress and combat boots that I wore
礼裙和靴子 作为“声明”
all the way through freshmen year ... as a "statement."
对 忘了它
Yeah. Forget that…
忘记那辆我撞了就跑的车
forget that car that I hit and then sped away,
我还从没告诉过别人 直到现在
and didn't tell anyone. Until now.
实际上是三辆
Actually it was three.
神马
What?
到你了到你了
Go, go!
好好好
Okay, okay, okay!
呃...忘掉那个让我签了卖身契
Uh, forget the MasterI had for five years
为他工作了五年的主人
who kept me in indentured servitude…
卧槽
What?
这是醉话吧
It's probably the beer talking.
我大概说完该忘记的坏事了
I guess I ran out of bad shit to forget.
想像下 如果我们真的能忘记那些事
Imagine we could really forget all of that stuff ...
我们还剩下什么
what would we have left?
哦 天啊
Oh, my God...
其实只有啤酒和披萨也挺好的 对吧
You know, have been fine with just beer and pizza, right?
她现在才告诉我
Now she tells me.
你想怎么做
So, what's the plan?
该让这个恶灵上我的身了
It's time for me to introduce myself to this Jumbee.
等等
Wait...
是你
you?
你不应该这样做的
You shouldn't have done that.
你不该干预这些和你没关的事
You shouldn't be meddling in things that don't concern you!
很明显 你和这个世界脱节好久了
Clearly, you haven't been out in the world for a while,
让我来带你领略一下新世纪吧
so let me get you up to speed.
你好 我是Bo 不结盟淫妖
Hi, I'm Bo, the unaligned Succubus,
你好
how are you?
我的一些兴趣爱好有 皮衣 纵情欢乐
A couple things about me ...I like leather, having a good time,
还有 如果你没有注意到的话
and in case you haven't noticed ...
我总是爱多管闲事
I always meddle in things that don't concern me.
如果你不停止骚扰这些无辜的人
And if you don't stop torturing these innocent people
别怪我踢飞你的复古臀
I'm gonna crack my foot off in your retro ass!
折磨他们
Torturing them!?
他们以为我是巫婆
They thought I was a witch.
喂喂 拜托 小子们
Hey, hey...come on, boys,
我们说好了的
we talked about this...
把你的手拿开
Take your hands off her!
不准伤害她
Don't you hurt her!
放开我 让她走
Get your hands off me! Let her go!!!
John!
Jessie!
Noah!!!
他们向我的未婚夫 我的Noah
And they wanted my fiancee my Noah,
证明我是个女巫
to see me proved a witch.
别这样
Don't do this!!!
*中世纪鉴别女巫的方法，把女人浸水里如没窒息而死则是女巫*
求你了
Please!
元素妖精不是女巫
An Elemental ain't no witch!
我的Noah看到了我的真身
My Noah saw what I really was
他还是爱我
and he still loved me.
不
No!
他们把我们永远地分开了
They left us separate forever.
在Jenkins家族灭门前
And I ain't never gonna stop until every last one
我是不会停止的
of them Jenkins' is dead!
他们杀了他
They killed her.
你的祖先杀了她
Your ancestors killed her.
她和她未婚夫 也是Jenkins家族的
Her and her fiance also a Jenkins, murdered her!
哦天啊
Oh, God!
真是仇恨无限 痛苦多多
So much anger!So much pain!
她不会停手的
She's never gonna stop!
他们的做的事为什么算到我头上
Why are they making me pay for what they did??
因为昨日总是在呼唤
Because the past always comes calling.
她要占据主导了
She's trying to take over!
打败她 Bo
Fight her, Bo!
作为人类来说不错啊
Not bad. For a human.
那个 我一直都随你处置来着
Well, I am always at your disposal.
随我处置？
Disposal?
我喜欢
I like that.
那是什么
What was that?
我在Vex桌子后面那个小黑屋的时候
When I was in the cell behind Vex's desk,
真是思绪万千
I had a lot of time to think.
我发现了件很重要的事
I realized something very important.
哦
Oh?
你发现了什么
What did you realize?
就是我太过仁慈了
That I've been far too nice.
我就知道我抓不住那个淫妖
I know that Succubus was somehow behind my capture.
是时候有个人治治她了
It's time somebody finally put her in her place.
我已经把她解决了
I already did.
什么
Excuse me?
她已经消失了
She's gone.
我帮Tamsin搞定了她
I helped Tamsin get rid of her.
为了你
For you.
我在想也许我该回来
You know, I've been thinking maybe I should come back here.
我可以再和你住一起
I could live here with you again.
哦 亲
Oh...honey...
那我的狗该养哪啊
but then where would I keep the dogs?
你现在准备干什么
What are you gonna do now?
都没有Bo了
With Bo gone?
老娘干啥不行
Everything.
永远分开
Separate forever!
啥
What?
永远分开 是恶灵说的
Separate forever.That's what the Jumbee said!
我知道我们要干什么了
I know what we have to do!
他们结婚前就被杀了
Before they were married, they were killed!
他们没埋一起
They were buried separately!
要是我们
If we…
怎样
If we what?
人家举手了 人家回答
No, no, I know!
要把他们埋一起
If we bury them together
恶灵就不用复仇了
then it will end the Jumbee's need for vengeance.
不会吧 你都一千多岁了
Come on, you've been around for a thousand years,
就没读过琼瑶大妈的书？
and you've never read a romance novel?
哇 你这妹子真幸运
Wow, you are a lucky girl.
把Kathy 带下楼 锁好门
Take Kathy downstairs and lock yourselves up.
当心点 好吗
Be okay, okay?
Dyson你得去找他们的遗体
Dyson, you have to go find their remains, ok?
赶快
Just please hurry.
我不要离开你 Bo
I'm not leaving you, Bo!
我刚找到你
I just found you!
我绝对不要
There's no way in hell I'm...
你相信我吗
Do you trust me?
是的
Yes.
那么相信我
Then trust this.
我打得过她 Dyson
I can fight her, Dyson,
但是你必须离开
but you have to go.
你必须抓紧 拜托了 赶紧离开吧
You have to hurry! Please, just go!
好 这是他的腿骨还是恶灵的腿骨
Ok, is this his leg bone or the Jumbee's leg bone?
没关系 反正它们会被放在同一个地方
Doesn't matter.It's all going in the same place.
你和Bo平常约会都是做这些吗
Is this how your dates with Bo usually go?
挖坟拯救人类
Digging up graves, and trying to save human lives?
要是我说
I'd be lying if I said
这没有引起怀旧之情 那是假的
this didn't have some semblance of nostalgia.
好了 都在这了
Okay, that's it…
他俩骨头都捡全了吗？
are all of his bits with her bits?
全了
Yeah, they are.
好
Yeah
帮我拦住她
Help me hold her down.
噢 我会开心地杀掉你们俩
Oh, I'm gonna enjoy killing you both.
把她抓紧
Hold her still...
他们没有结婚
They were never married!
所以她还徘徊人间
That's why she's still stuck in limbo.
如果我们让他们结婚
If we marry them ...
也许痛苦就会结束了
maybe it will end the pain...
你在哪儿找到这些的
Where did you find these?
我许诺你成为我的法定妻子
I take you to be my lawfully wed wife
无论富有还是贫穷 健康或者不适
To have and to hold, in sickness and in health,
甚至死亡
and even in death.
你是否愿意让我成为你的
Do you take me to be your...
Noah
Noah...
你是否愿意让Noah成为你的法定丈夫
Do you take Noah to be your lawfully wedded husband?
无论富有还是贫穷 健康或者不适
To have and to hold, in sickness and in health,
甚至死亡
even in death?
我愿意
Yes.I do.
你们在看啥啊
What are you guys looking at?
你看不见他们吗
You can't see them?
等等
Wait...
我们……？
Are we?
准备好回家了吗
Ready to go home?
杠杠的
Oh, hells yes.
走吧
Yeah.
早上好 Ronny
Good morning, Ronny!
接电话好吗
Grab the phone, would ya?
有个乡巴佬每隔十分钟就打电话来
Some yahoo's been calling every ten minutes or so,
找一个叫Karen的人
asking about some Karen.
什么
What?
是的 说提供她的信息可以得到悬赏
Yeah. Said there's a big reward for information.
我都没时间准备自己的事了
Hardly had time to do my prep.
红毛 你会接电话吧
You gonna answer it, Red?
我得去趟洗手间
I actually have to go to the washroom.
啊 你的靴子都破破烂烂的了
Uh, your kicks are gone all ghetto.
你想借我的小猫眯飞靴么
Oh, you want to borrow my kitten heel fly boots.
它们可是各种奢华 或许可以让
They are trés gorge and they might make
你穿的这身乞丐装
this, um, homeless-persons-nighty-thing you're rockin'
看起来高端大气上档次
look like an actual fashion choice.
你知道我为什么直觉你没事吗
You know how I know you're gonna be okay?
因为你的胆子和我最好的朋友一样大
Because you've got balls as big as my best friend.
她是个妹子啦
Who is a girl?
噢
Oh...
再见 宝贝 别对他们太苛刻了
Bye, babe.And don't be so hard on them.
总有一天 你必须面对你自己的恶魔
One day you might have to face down your own demons...
而他们或许会帮得上大忙
and they might come in handy.
不过如果你需要我
But if you do ever need me...
来找我就行
come find me.
我得走了
I need to leave.
什么
What?
出城 我得出城
Town.I need to leave town.
你在说什么啊 什么时候走
What are you talking about? Leave when?
现在就走
Now!
听着 我说不清
Look I can't really explain...
我 我跟你一起走 好吗
I... will come with you, ok?
我能帮上忙
I can help ...
不行
No.
只用答应我 要是有任何人来找我的话
Look just promise me.If anybody comes looking for me,
你就装作你不认识我
you'll pretend that you never knew me.
你要去哪儿 就...
Where are you going? Just...
答应我
Promise me.
我答应
Promise.
祝你好运
For luck.
真心希望你能有点运气
I really hope you find some soon.
等下等下
Wait, wait, wait...
这里有别的路可以出去吗
is there another way out of here?
有 来吧
Yeah. Come on.
不舒服还这么着急
You're in an awful rush for a sick girl?
我就是等不及回床上了
I just can't wait to get into bed.
头等大事当然优先
First thing's first.
Clio  你要搞那个吹耳神功不
Clio...you wanna do that ear thing?
你以为你在干嘛
What do you think you're doing?
拿属于我的东西喽
Taking what's mine.
有钱能使鬼推磨 而你的小伙伴 Vex
Money talks, and your buddy, Vex,
有钱多得没处花啊
has got boat loads of it.
你真的觉得自己能带着她离开
Do you really think you're just gonna walk away with her?
我这么说吧
Let me put it this way.
要是你跟上来或者想制止我
If you follow us or try to stop me,
我就让穿越后遗症
then I'm gonna let the transcendental sickness
吞了她的五脏六腑 然后我就把她
eat her insides and then I'm gonna leave her
留在一片激烈又血腥的淫脑混乱之中
in a hot and bloody succubus mess.
我不是说远离我
I don't mean walk away from me.
我是说远离她
I mean walk away from her.
啥
What?
上次我百度的时候 恶灵也是元素精灵吧
Last time I checked, Jumbees were Elementals, too.
啊
Ahhh!
看吧 助人为乐就这么回事儿 Clio
See, that's the thing about helping people, Clio.
有的时候回报你的东西叫因果报应
Sometimes you get paid back with a little thing called Karma.
啊
Ow!
恶灵已经治愈了我
Jumbee already healed me.
她在你身体里的时候
And when she was inside of you
看见了你真正的目的
she saw exactly what you were up to.
真是砖家
This is just professional...
你知不知道老娘有多烦多恶心
Do you have any idea how sick and tired I am of being
被人呼来唤去 骗得团团转吗
double crossed and lied to and generally dicked around?!
想欺负妹子 挑错人了吧
You picked the wrong girl to screw over.
因为老娘就喜欢以牙还牙
Because I like to make everything personal.
啊
Ow...
你是何方妖孽
What are you?
她是你大姨妈
She's your worst nightmare.
含笑九泉
Dying with a smile...
那算是太便宜你了
that is much too good a fate for you.
你失踪穿越到中世纪了
Did you get a little medieval while you were away?
不知道
I don't know.
可能吧
Maybe.
哦
Oh...
喂
Hey...
这么说
So...
是Vex是吧
Vex, huh?
艾玛他能不能早点选边啊
Man, can that guy pick a team already?
说得容易
You're one to talk.
*Bo自己就没站队*
天哪 我好想你
God, I missed you.
我也想你
I missed you too.
带我回家
Take me home?
说对了
You got it.
好
Yeah.
嗯 我等不及要见大家了
Hmm...I can't wait to see everyone.
Kenzi和Hale...
Kenzi and Hale...
Trick和...
Trick and...
找个日子 我们得谈谈
You know, some day we're gonna have to talk about
火车上发生的事
what happened on that train.
啥火车？
What train?
不知道
I don't know.
不知道我怎么会说那个
I don't know why I said that...
别担心
Don't worry.
我会搞清楚自己是怎么了
I will figure out what happened to me.
无论如何都会的
One way or another.
这点你放心吧
You can be sure of that.
我是甩不掉你了是不
I'm not gonna get rid of you, am I?
没那么容易
Not that easy.
上车吧亲
Hop in, partner.
知道不
You know what?
见到你我真的很高兴
I am really happy to see you.
我很抱歉
And I'm really sorry.
为什么
Why?
你觉得我们要不要停车看看他们要不要帮忙
You think we should stop and see if they need help?
对不起 Bo
Sorry, Bo...
得先送你回家了
gotta get you home.
自家轮胎瘪了是个人都能修好
Whoever that is can fix their own flat tire.